A long time ago,
a Primal Orb arose
born from chaos.
The Supreme Lord
split the unruly Orb in two.
From its light,
came the Spirit Pearl,
and its dark, the Demon Orb.
But the dark half was marked
by a curse from Heaven,
which in three years
would annihilate it
with divine lightning.
Later, due to the sabotage
of Shen Gongbao,
the dark half was reborn
as Lord Li Jing's third son,
Nezha.
And the light
became the third son
of the Loong King, Ao Bing.
By fate, lost halves met,
and soon, they became
the best of friends.
Nezha raised hell,
but through his parents' love,
tamed his nature
and saved Chentang Pass.
Hand in hand with Ao Bing,
they faced Heaven's Wrath,
and at last,
were able to change their fate.
Though you survived
the lightning,
both your bodies
were destroyed,
and without physical forms,
soon oblivion
will claim your souls.
The Sacred Lotus
protects and nurtures spirit.
I'll now use its heavenly power
to remake your forms.
Sick.
Oh, my.
Let's go!
-They're cooking?
-That's the way.
They powder the lotus,
so you can be rebuilt.
Hey, did you just scratch
your foot with that hand?
Oh, it's fine.
I never did mind a sticky foot.
-I'll just wash it.
-I don't care about your foot.
Ugh.
Did you just blow your nose?
What do mean? This?
Oh, bless your heart.
It's lotus powder.
See that now? Lotus powder.
Powder's ready to go.
Yep, here it is.
One booger for each of you.
I mean, uh, one serving.
Time's a-wasting.
Would you rather die?
Yes, I'd rather die.
Quit making a fuss, now go!
It really worked!
- The heck is this?
- Hey, thanks, kid.
Been searching high and low
for that.
Uh...
Flying Piggy!
My ride has a perfect memory.
And is a master sculptor
to boot.
Take a look for yourselves.
Thank you, Piggy.
No, no, no. Don't move!
You're still mushy.
Master, I've mobilized
all of Chentang Pass' forces.
We're ready for Shen Gongbao
and the Eastern Sea Loongs.
Relax! The Loongs
are watching the Abyss monsters.
You won't see
any coming your way.
Besides, Shen Gongbao alone
is no threat.
You both gotta
come check this out!
Good as new, huh?
He learned from the best.
Okay. We don't have to settle
for the same look, right?
-How about a makeover?
-Huh?
Uh...
That's right.
How about a little makeover
for our son?
Make me a beefcake.
But gorgeous like a prince.
A man
must be strong and masculine.
- Don't forget handsome!
- Yet cute as a button.
Can you all please
make up your minds?
Make me a beefcake!
But stunning like a prince.
-Tall and strapping.
-Yet cute as a button.
-What's this, huh?
-He says you're on your own.
Fine. Want something done right?
Then you better do it yourself.
This could take a while.
Why don't we do you first, then?
You were born of water,
so the water
shall make you whole!
Voilà.
That's more like it.
Are you done yet?
Almost there.
Obviously, this is the best one,
but it may still need
a little bit of work
-Let's just use the first one.
-Yeah. The first one, please.
Mmm. Yes, the first.
You were born of fire,
so flames
shall complete your form!
Sir! Enemy approaching.
We think it's Shen Gongbao.
-How many are there?
-It's only him.
He's here alone?
You finish the spell.
We'll deal with our guest.
Please,
let me plead with my master.
Don't move!
Another stick of incense
has to burn before you're fixed.
Shen Gongbao.
To what do we owe this honor?
Now that you know what
the Loongs and I are planning,
I cannot help but feel un--
Uneasy.
Chentang Pass is heavily guarded
and Master Taiyi's still within.
If you've come here alone,
you won't accomplish much.
Did...?
Did someone say
I came here alone?
Once they know
that you stole the Spirit Pearl,
you'll fail to avenge your son,
and the East Loong Clan...
will all bear the blame.
When the truth comes out,
you'll be cast into purgatory
to burn alongside
all your old "friends."
We can't wait to welcome you!
If you're stuck down here,
how will you find justice
for your son?
Things don't look good for you.
You wretched fools
are in no position to gloat.
I just wanted to help.
But it seems
you're not appreciative.
Seems you've forgotten
what I'm capable of.
But I know! The Sky--
The Sky--
-The Sky--
-Sky Splitting Claw. Thank you.
Master Shen can take this claw
with him to Chentang Pass
and use its power
to tear open a rift
leading back to me.
And the Abyss monsters can help
destroy your enemy.
Abyss monsters?
But how? How is that possible?
They were trapped by
the Suppression Seal for years.
How could they have escaped?
The Loongs.
Did they release them?
With the Sea-Stabilizing Chains
binding us, no one will suspect
we were behind this.
This is a win-win tactic.
What do you say, brother?
You won't do it for free.
Well, then, what's your price?
In this prison,
where flames cook flesh,
days are as years.
If you could lower
the lava's heat,
easing our great torment,
all the strength we have
would be yours.
Hm? What was that?
What--?
What's Shen Gongbao up to now?
Finally, we're out. Yay!
Bye-bye!
-Bad Yaksha!
-We're doomed.
How will we explain this
to General Li?
-Luckily, no one saw us. Here.
-A rock?
I'll break your arms
and you break my legs.
We'll say it was the Yaksha.
Oh, when the general sees
how badly we were hurt,
we won't be blamed
for his escape.
-Come on, weakling.
-You're the weakling.
Hey.
Hey!
Hey, you two!
Huh?
Master,
I didn't see you there.
He let the Yaksha escape.
Huh? What are you saying?
It was all because of you
that he got free!
-Don't point fingers.
-Don't play innocent.
It's Dumb and Dumber.
Hey! You two boneheads,
get over here right now
and guard me!
-Yes, sir, right away.
-We're coming.
Show no mercy.
Shen Gongbao!
Ao Bing is not dead.
Chentang Pass and the Loongs
need not go to war.
Taiyi is rebuilding
Ao Bing's body as we speak.
Lies won't save you. Hmm?
The shield.
No!
Master. Master!
Ao Bing.
Master Taiyi's built me
a new body.
You have to stop fighting.
Shen Gongbao.
I saved your disciple.
How about a "thank you"?
There, is it Nezha
in that Lotus?
Why, I-- You son of a donkey!
-Master!
-All who know must die!
You think that you can
break through this shield?
Take your best shot.
Come on. I'm waiting!
No!
That aura...
-Ao Bing.
-Father.
Father. I failed my mission
to save our kind.
No. That doesn't matter now.
You save your energy.
Long as you're safe,
that's enough for me.
Open.
-Why is your body fading?
-Come on, it's a new body.
There's no way he could survive
-a hit like that.
-Ao Bing!
Hey! Hold up, stay put.
Don't move, kiddo.
Ao Bing, what's going on?
Your body's not settled yet.
Why are you running?
If you push your new body
too hard like that,
it's gonna fall apart,
for heaven's sake.
Hey, Fatty! Get over here
and make another body
for Ao Bing right now. Huh?
Making two back-to-back,
it's drained the Sacred Lotus.
But without a body,
won't his soul scatter?
-Master, do something!
-Without the Sacred Lotus,
I can't do anything.
No, it's all right.
This started because we took
the Spirit Pearl.
If my sacrifice
can make right that wrong,
then it's a fair price to pay.
Who asked you to do that?
I'm cool with being
the Demon Orb, okay?
Don't you dare die!
Father.
Please spare Chentang Pass.
Our past mistakes,
they've got to end.
This is my final wish.
There must be a way.
Something we haven't tried.
You must know. Tell me now!
Let him share your body for now.
Share your body.
Two souls both sharing
the same body?
Success is impossible.
The Spirit Pearl and Demon Orb
were part of a whole.
Sharing for just one week
shouldn't be a problem for them.
That's it!
Ao Bing, come on in. Quick!
Okay.
Wow, this feels really weird.
Ao Bing, are you there?
Yes, I am.
I can hear your voice
in my head.
Oh, man, this is so cool.
But just as a temporary fix.
What happens
when the week's done?
There's a potion
in the Yu Xu Palace vault.
Elixir Reparo!
It can restore any magic item.
We pour the Elixir on
and the Sacred Lotus
will bloom again!
But how will you obtain it?
I'll go beg the Supreme Lord
for some.
Or maybe you'll
tell him about what we did?
The Supreme Lord
won't s-save a Loong prince.
If he says no,
we'll just take it.
Yu Xu Palace is
Chan Sect's heart. Impregnable.
For my son, I'll storm
heaven itself if I have to.
Your Majesty, calm down.
I might have a plan.
Chan Sect disciples who excel
may try the Ascension Trial.
Passing grants
not only immortality,
but also the right
to choose one magic item
from Yu Xu Vault.
You're saying Nezha should take
the trial to get the elixir?
Bad idea, bad idea.
The kid's full of demon energy.
If he uses his powers,
he'll give himself away!
Isn't Ao Bing
sharing Nezha's body?
His aura can mask
the dark energy.
As long as he passes in a week,
not only will we obtain
the e-elixir, but also--
I'll be an immortal. Uh...
That means
I won't be a demon anymore.
Saving Ao Bing as well as Nezha.
E-Everyone wins.
Lying like this is wrong.
Then what do you suggest?
Follow the rules.
We tell the truth and trust
in Supreme Lord's judgment.
My wife and I
will also plead your case,
so the parents' sins aren't
passed on to the children.
Mortal ignorance.
Only decades alive
and you lecture me
on what's right and wrong!
Living for so long,
there's much you forget,
but if there's one truth
I've learned
over thousands of years,
it's that if my son dies,
then Chentang Pass
will die with him.
Stop!
Ao Bing is my friend.
I'll save him, I promise.
But if you dare
touch Chentang Pass,
I'll smash your Loong Palace
into pieces!
Except for Nezha and Taiyi,
no one leaves Chentang Pass
from this moment onward.
If in seven days,
there's no Elixir,
or if anyone learns
my clan's secret,
all of Chentang Pass
will be forfeit.
I don't trust my siblings
and I can't stay
out of my body for long.
Chentang Pass' fate,
I leave in your hands.
Simple.
There isn't that anything
that can't be said
with just a simple nod.
General! We're all here
to bid farewell
to Young Master Nezha.
We wanted to thank him
for saving Chentang Pass.
You're too kind.
Over all these years,
he's caused enough trouble.
I always knew the Young Master
was destined for greatness.
Just look at him.
A warrior's brow,
perfect dimples,
a sharp sniffer,
and what a jaw he has.
All signs of a hero of legend.
I'm never wrong about faces.
Young Master,
remember to brush your teeth
after meals.
Boss man.
The Demon Slayers
are now the Nezha Gang.
All gang members
will follow your orders.
Wanna learn to write,
young master? I'm your guy.
You're 3 years old now.
Time to get a girlfriend.
Wanna learn to play?
We'll teach you them all.
I want to play jianzi!
What? Come on, it's fun.
Anyone?
I'll play.
You've been asking me to play
jianzi with you for ages.
Wait, his kicks
are a little hard.
I am a general.
-Dad.
-Yup, that's my boy.
How about we do something else?
Nonsense, son.
Why stop now
when you're having fun?
It's fine. I'm fine.
I'll also join in.
My love, you don't have to--
You think I'm some weakling?
I'm a general too.
Nezha, catch this.
Hey, sweetheart,
how did you miss that one?
If only I was normal.
What was that?
Nothing! I should get going.
Before you leave,
will you give your mama
one last big hug?
Come on, they're all watching.
Wait, wait!
I made a bag
of all your favorite snacks.
For you
and your master to share.
Okay, okay. Let's go.
Hey, I'm not on board yet!
You're body's still settling.
So don't yourself push too hard.
I know!
Watch your temper.
Try to stay calm out there.
Mom and Dad won't be there.
So stay safe for us, okay?
Ah, real mature, kid.
Would a quick hug
really have killed you?
It would've been awkward.
It's not a farewell anyway.
Giddyup!
What's the matter?
Food taste bad?
Is food all you think about?
Just look at me.
I'm too worried to eat.
Have you even thought about
how to pass the trial?
What's it even about?
Everything you've ever learned.
In front of the Trial judges,
you must beat
three Earthly Immortal-level
demon lords, barehanded.
Fighting, my specialty.
But the jig is up the moment
you use your demon powers.
Then just let Ao Bing
control my body.
His spirit energy
will mask my power.
Mm. That easy, huh?
Then let's try it.
Nezha, relax your body.
Now hand the reins over
to Ao Bing and come at me.
Ao Bing. What you doing?
Stand still.
When two souls share one body,
unless your willpower is
much stronger than the host's,
then you won't be able
to fully control it.
Nezha, easy now.
The harder you push,
the less Ao Bing can control.
Use your leg. Sweep. Sweep.
Ha-ha!
- Don't panic!
- Your master to the res--
--cue.
Think this is funny, huh?
Time's running out
and you're still messing around.
Look at you.
What kind of master are you?
Stand over there
and think about what you did.
And no more food
until you have a plan!
Aren't you like
a thousand years old?
Quit acting like such a child.
I got it.
-The Sleepy-Slumber Pill.
-What's that?
Take this
and it'll knock you right out.
Once you're sleeping,
then Ao Bing
can take full control
of your body.
Oh, yeah.
Ah-ah-ah! One is enough.
Wait, what?
Aw, crap.
Perfect.
Master?
Oh, now this feels like
the real deal.
Is something wrong?
Oh! Don't worry, it's nothing.
Now that you have full control
of Nezha's body, let's go again.
This time around,
I won't hold back.
Give it your best shot.
How can I improve, master?
Not bad, kid. No match
for me yet, but good effort.
Master, your nose is bleeding.
Huh? Oh, it's just the heat.
Need to drink more water.
I'm good. I'm good. Huh?
Kunlun Mountain! We're here.
So a day here
equals a year at home?
Relax. We're not
in the celestial realm yet.
All those pilgrims!
They've all come
for immortality.
Everyone wants to join
the world-famous Chan Sect.
Here, take a look. Jasper.
A Chan Sect immortal's badge.
Now, with this, everyone will
start showing you some respect.
-Pretty cool, huh?
-Immortality.
Both your brothers
have ascended.
You'll have no problem either.
Oh, I mean, Nezha's brothers.
His two brothers
are among the best
of our third-generation
disciples.
Wanna know something?
Nezha's always acting up, right?
Well, I often tell him stories
of his brothers' heroics
to set a good example.
Between us, Ao Bing,
Nezha idolizes them big-time.
Oh, wow, lucky you!
You get to see
the legendary Demon Hunters.
Demon Hunters?
They roam the land,
hunting down demons
that wreak havoc on humanity,
and keep the peace.
The leader of the Demon Hunters
is the top disciple
of Immortal Wuliang.
Hey, wasn't his predecessor
Shen Gongbao?
Master,
what's that smoke over there?
Oh, that's the most
precious treasure
of Yu Xu Palace,
The Tianyuan Cauldron.
Brother, it's been forever.
Brother Wuliang.
I heard master
went into seclusion
and you are now steward
to the Yu Xu Palace.
I've brought my disciple
for the Ascension Trial.
Nezha, pay your respect
to Master Wuliang.
-Master Wuliang.
-So you're Nezha?
The Spirit Pearl?
Oh...
How impressive you are.
Our master's expectations
for you are high.
Don't disappoint now.
Look, everybody.
He's practically glowing.
And what kind eyes.
Huh?
The boy's been training
too much.
He's still a bit pig-lagged.
Ah!
What do you think you're doing?
We're inside the Yu Xu Palace.
I gotta pee.
-Crana.
-Here.
Take him
to the little boys' room.
What was that?
Who you calling little?
What a weirdo.
The little boys' room
is the place you go
when you have to pee.
The boy forgets
his manners sometimes.
Pay him no mind.
Wow, so white.
Is the entire palace
made of jade?
Where'd they get the money
to buy all of it?
The word "Yu" in Yu Xu Palace
stands for jade, right?
Then what does the "Xu" mean?
Humble? Guilty? Or emptiness?
Uh, are the toilets jade too?
Do Immortals need to go pee?
Does Wuliang also poop?
This hall's sacred.
Lower your voice.
How far is it?
I'm gonna explode!
Hey, miss, wait for me.
You...
-Uh, I didn't mean to.
-I need to change.
Go by yourself.
But I don't even know
where to go.
Down the hall,
then turn right, then left.
Oh.
Wow, Immortals have it so good,
even the toilet's jade.
Uh... Am I lost?
Where are you going?
Oh! I got lost.
Come along.
Well done raising
the Spirit Pearl, brother.
A grand achievement.
For you and our order.
Oh, it's nothing.
It's all thanks
to master's guidance.
This Kunlun Dew,
it's a rare elixir.
Normally, it takes six months
to fill a basin.
But I just had someone check
and it was full.
Oh, your arrival
couldn't be timed better.
Brother, fortune sure seems
to favor you, doesn't it?
What's wrong with you?
-Ow!
-Can't you drink normally?
He needs
to work on his manners.
Pay him no mind.
My pee's in the water.
He needs to work on his manners.
Pay him no mind.
Brother, we're short on time.
I think that Nezha should
attempt the trial immediately.
Immediately?
Well, let's drink
some more first.
-Oh... No. No, thank you.
-Uh... Well, all right, then.
Hmm. Deero, my disciple,
will be the trial judge.
The Demon Hunters' next target,
that could be
Nezha's first test.
Brother, excuse us.
My dear brother,
always in a such a hurry.
Mmm. The taste
of this year's dew is...
...quite full bodied.
You must keep using this method
from now on.
Of course.
Why did you stop?
It's been six hours,
Master Shen.
-We need a break, sir.
-Nonsense!
Sloth is our undoing.
Unless I say--
D-Don't stop throwing!
Lord Li here to see you, sir.
Master Shen, yesterday,
many of our people were injured.
Our stores are low.
I beg of you, open a path,
so doctors may leave
and gather medicine.
A bold request.
No wonder--
Who did that? Ah! Oh!
When I get my hands on--
I'll--
Stop, stop, stop!
The one you caught earlier.
Bring him here.
He fled the city
during the battle.
General Li, please.
Take him b-back with you.
Oh, this is one big mistake.
I'm a demon just like you.
This Yaksha, I captured him once
in order to clear my son's name.
Now that that's all settled
and since he hasn't done
anything wrong, just let him go.
Uh-huh, uh-huh. Yes, exactly.
I'm an extra!
A bit part.
I don't think
you understood me.
No one leaves this place,
not even a demon,
let alone humans.
Huh? Oh, Master Shen, mercy.
I'm a demon too.
Come on, both of us
are bad guys.
I'm not a bad guy.
Long as you know our secret,
you won't be leaving!
Without medicine, our wounded
won't last that long.
Master Shen, please.
Lives are at stake.
-Hmph!
-Sir! We caught a spy.
A human from outside the city.
He wounded some of our soldiers.
L-Lock him up too.
Brother? It's you, isn't it?
Huh? Is that--?
Brother, it's me!
Shen Xiaobao?
You haven't been home
for centuries.
I missed you so much!
-What are you doing here?
-Dad sent me to find you.
Look, the compass you gave me!
It tells me where you are.
Oh, ah.
Father. How is he? Well, I hope?
Oh, he's great.
Since you became immortal,
Dad's been a completely
different demon.
Like he took some elixir.
You're the only one of us
to make it into Yu Xu Palace.
Now, demons come from all over
to train with Dad.
Tell me,
what are you doing here?
You know how you said
once I could turn human,
you'd get me into Yu Xu Palace?
Well, check this out!
All these years,
I've been training so hard,
just like you used to do.
You're my role model, brother.
"Yu Xu Palace, savior of all.
A guiding light
for great and small."
By the way, brother.
What are you doing here?
What--? Oh. Uh...
Do all these monsters
work for you?
Why are you surrounding
Chentang Pass?
About that.
Uh, thing is--
Master Shen
is defending our city.
- Huh?
- We were beset by a great evil.
Master Shen and his troops
came to our aid.
On behalf of us all,
thanks for your noble rescue.
Of course. It's nothing.
Wow, you're a hero, big brother!
Is this the demon
who attacked the city?
Ah. Uh-huh.
You're a disgrace
to demons everywhere.
Shame on you.
Hey, uh, Xiaobao.
Can you wait a few more years
before joining us?
Huh? Wait, but why?
I just got my face down.
Uh, it's just...
I'm preparing to join
the Twelve and must focus.
Are you for real?
Once I see that through,
I'll take you there, okay?
You got it! Make us proud.
I can go to Yu Xu Palace
anytime.
Besides, my shape-shifting
still needs work.
I'll go practice more
till it's perfect.
Xiaobao, I've saved these
- since joining the sect.
- What are they?
Yu Xu Palace
gives all their disciples
immortality pills.
One will save you
ten years of hard work.
Wait, but this is way too much.
Brother, you'll need these,
so you can join the Twelve.
I've never liked the taste.
I'd rather train on my own.
You take them.
Share them with the family.
But Dad will be mad
if he finds out.
Xiaobao. I'm your big brother.
Take the pills and go home.
This is the front line.
If you don't,
I'll be distracted.
Then, well...
I'll go.
Brother! You gotta make it
into the Twelve!
And I'm gonna keep training too!
Thank you for your help,
but the stakes are too high
to let anyone leave.
This Yaksha--
You bring him back too.
You misunderstand.
That was for the young one.
A good role model
can really change his life.
Wait.
Leave--
Leave me your supply list.
Hmph!
I am Nezha,
the Third Prince bold.
I slay demons,
write rhymes untold.
Today, I come
to rid evil's breath.
You wicked fiends,
prepare for death!
You still eating?
You're going down, fur face.
Well, looks like
we got an intruder.
Bandit's Hill
ain't no place for a kid.
So you're in charge? Alrighty.
Come here and taste my fists.
You cocky little ankle-biter.
Hey, boss,
let's teach this brat a lesson.
Let's go, then.
-Uh... You go.
-Huh? B-But, boss!
I could never go
and steal your thunder.
I'm not gonna bully a half-pint.
When I say go, you go!
Hey, kid.
You're still young, naive,
so I'm willing to let you go.
It's still not too late
to run home to your mommy!
- Huh? What's wrong?
- Why are you awake?
I don't know. Can't sleep.
All your jumping around
must have woke me up.
Not good! He's built up
a tolerance to the pills.
-I need more.
-If you won't leave,
you might get hurt!
I was going to the right.
Sorry,
thought you were dodging left.
Huh?
And stay down, weakling.
Master,
maybe I should cut in now.
He could use
a few more years' training.
J-Just hold on.
He's just taunting them.
The boy likes to play dumb.
Pills, pills.
I need my pills.
Don't say I didn't warn ya!
Now you really know
just who you're messing with.
Oh, no.
The pills dissolved.
Then I'll just drink it.
Now you're stealing our
soup? Why, I-- Huh?
My turn.
Mighty Marmot Club!
See that?
Told you he was faking.
I missed you
on purpose. Again!
But how? He's just a kid.
Embarrassing! Don't get up.
-Let me show you how it's done.
-Why'd you just spit it out?
It was rancid.
I couldn't help it.
Take this!
That's good acting.
It's no use.
We can't win without the pill.
Deero is watching.
I can't give you the pill.
-What to do? What to do?
-I know there is another way.
- You don't mean...?
- We can eat the throw-up.
But that's disgusting!
It's fine.
Remember when I drank
Yaksha booger?
Now I see it.
That unyielding drive.
His unbending will.
That's how Nezha defeated fate.
My friends and family
are counting on me.
So is all of Chengtang Pass!
Whatever it takes,
I will save them!
Rejecting ancient bias.
Overcoming inner demons!
I will change my destiny!
I kept it pretty low-key,
but my secret's out now,
I guess.
- Master...
- Save Nezha first.
The Elixir's
gonna have to wait.
There's no way. It can't be!
Kid, let's go another round.
Playing possum?
Then I'll crush you!
Good thing
Nezha got knocked out!
It's okay, little baby.
Don't worry, I'll avenge you.
Super rodent punch!
Huh?
We must catch them all?
Leaving one could harm
the people living here.
So we'll take them all.
The Sect will guide them
to the right path,
turning evil good.
Why has his face changed?
Ah! Oh, it's nothing.
He changes his look
from time to time. Spirit Pearl.
Not your average kid, you know.
Next time be more careful.
You scared me to death!
So who's the kid?
His name's Nezha.
Jinzha and Muzha's brother.
The Supreme Lord appointed him
to be the Spirit Pearl.
Oh, so that's him, huh?
Doesn't really look
the part though, does he?
That pig-shaped schnoz,
stains on his shirt.
And with those bags
under his eyes.
Looks like a raccoon.
Or a raccoon's ghost.
Ah-ah-ah! Drop it, drop it.
Brother,
what's the star sign tonight?
A six-star alignment!
That's once a decade!
When six stars align,
each jade podium is able
to share both sight and sound.
Since the Twelve each live
so far, this lets us meet.
Tonight is a perfect
six-star conjunction.
Quite ideal for our summit.
Oh, but I'm not part
of the Twelve yet.
-Maybe I should step out.
-No, it won't be long.
No la, no la.
It's not appropriate.
I just couldn't. Really.
-Then why are you sitting there?
-Shut up! Let me have this one.
Ah! Oh!
- A sauna!
- Shh!
Brothers and sisters, welcome!
Greetings, Wuliang.
Let me introduce our newest
member, Brother Taiyi.
He's done the Supreme Lord proud
and raised the Spirit Pearl
to serve the Light.
Show some respect!
The Deification War
is soon upon us.
That's why we've gathered,
to discuss preparations.
Chan Sect's Tao orthodoxy,
we are destined to win.
But as Jie Sect rises throughout
the world, we must act soon.
Jie Sect is
a gaggle of barbarous filth
and creatures
born of mucus and eggs.
This war concerns our survival.
We must tread cautiously.
Strengthening our numbers
is our best strategy.
I quite agree.
Which is why I've begun
preparation early.
Immortality pills?
Nine thousand total.
For the entire Chan Sect,
to be shared based on rank.
These will surely give us
the edge we require,
-but how are there so many?
-For a century,
our master refined them
with the Tianyuan Cauldron,
working all hours at the cost
of his own health and training.
Our dear brother, you've
sacrificed much for our sect.
We're all in your debt.
Thank you, brother.
Jie Sect aside, what other evil
forces plot against our order?
Master Cihang,
as soon as a threat emerges,
the Demon Hunters
are sent forth.
So most monster clans
pose little threat to us.
But there has been
one exception.
-Oh? An exception?
-The Sea Loongs.
Didn't they surrender
to Heaven's Court long ago?
Any demon's word is suspect.
In my opinion,
they feign surrender
out in the open
and plot in secret.
But they've kept
the Abyss monsters
in check for millennia.
What are their real crimes?
It's their strength
that's my concern.
If they betray us in the war,
the balance
might shift against us.
We'll leave them be.
The bedrock
of our reputation is justice.
To launch an attack and without
a shred of evidence...
Well, then, all trust
we once had would be lost.
I concur.
-But they are--
-Enough.
They have all made fair points,
and bigotry is wrong.
Sir.
The alignment is almost over.
Since there's nothing else to
discuss, I propose we adjourn.
Brother.
Jinzha and Muzha are disciples
of myself and Brother Puxian.
They've been away
for many years,
so they've never met Nezha,
their younger brother.
Since there's time
before the stars separate,
we thought it might be nice for
them to get to know each other.
Mmm! Splendid idea.
Oh, no. What do I do?
What do I do?
Do? About what?
I mean, look at me.
What are they gonna think?
They'll think I'm a freak.
-Of course not.
-Really?
Even though you're lazy,
you never give up.
Even though you're small,
you have the biggest heart.
Even though
you're hard to look at,
you're kind on the inside.
Even with your raccoon eye bags,
pig nose,
and a missing tooth,
I still think you're...
you're perfect
just the way you are.
And I'm sure
that your brothers would agree.
That's right. Keep it coming.
-The pills!
-You meet them for me.
Wait, but seriously,
how can I do this for you?
No, Nezha. Nezha!
Ah!
Look how shy he is.
- Nezha!
- Hey, bro.
Ao Bing, are you crying?
Yes. Seeing them
reminded me of my brothers.
You have brothers too?
Mm. Used to.
Having two wonderful brothers,
you're lucky.
What did you guys talk about?
They said they're sorry
for not checking on you
all these years.
They asked a lot.
How things have been
at Chentang Pass.
If your parents are well,
if you play jianzi,
and who your friends are.
They also said that
if you ever needed anything,
you should go to them.
And to remember,
your brothers will always
be there to look after you.
-Huh? Why are you...?
-Nothing!
It's just eyes in my sand.
You sure it's not
the other way around?
Shut up! You know what I meant!
Heh. Whatever you say.
You're the worst!
All right, all right.
I promise I'll stop, okay?
Are you still mad at me,
Nezha? Nezha?
-Ao Bing?
-Yeah?
I've been a menace
since day one.
My parents worry about me
all the time.
And your dad, even though
he attacked Chentang Pass,
I know it was for you.
And just now, my brothers
were both so kind to me.
Our families
have sacrificed a lot for us.
You're a monster. I'm a demon.
We're both our family's burdens.
So, what if I was born a demon?
Who I get to be?
Only I get to make that choice!
After you get your body back,
we're both becoming Immortals,
and we'll make
our families proud!
Yes! Immortals! And then
we can chart our own course!
It's a deal!
I'm gonna be immortal!
Strength. Diligence.
Progress demands these virtues.
But, at your speed, a hundred
years wouldn't be enough.
In your training, you must hone
your endurance and spirit.
Feeling tired? Giving up?
That's because every last
one of you was born a demon!
Only through sacrifice
can you become an immortal
and change your fate!
Life or death,
of none I'm scared.
What fate says,
I've never cared.
My fate is mine,
not heaven's plan.
This boy will be
an immortal man!
Bravo!
Only one stanza, yet so moving.
How inspiring.
Great poem. Good work.
The spirit of his words
is something you should all
take to heart.
Really? It was that good?
I kind of just made it up.
It was that good!
The message is quite inspiring.
To craft
such well-metered verse,
that takes some real ambition,
young man.
The mark of a true hero
with a bright future.
Ah, come on,
it was just all right.
Actually,
I changed a couple of things--
Your face, on the other hand.
Tell me,
what's wrong with your eyes?
It's a clear tale
that you stay up late,
that you lack discipline
and just eat junk,
that you can't manage
basic self-control,
and you dream of ascension?
My eyes are always like this.
Appearance reflects the heart.
Have you checked a mirror
lately? You look ridiculous!
If you were my disciple, I'd
make you build a whole new form.
Really?
You can change the way I look?
It's not too late?
You gotta teach me!
I knew you came
to find a master.
Listen, young one. It's clear
that you have great ambition,
so I'll take you as my disciple.
Cool! Master!
Come, train with your brothers.
-For what?
-Ascension!
I don't need help with that.
Just my face.
Absurd! You're putting
your looks before training?
-You missed the point.
-You gonna teach me, or what?
We're no longer
master and apprentice.
You deserve to have panda eyes
for life!
Hey, that's rude. I was
gonna go easy on you, but...
-What's this, a challenge?
-Three should do it.
Young one, go back
to where you came from.
If you keep this up,
you'll be in for
a different kind of lesson. Huh?
-Huh?
-Apologies.
You're no match for me.
Impressive.
I underestimated you!
Take this!
How is he so fast?
Did you see that?
I'll hold no grudge toward you,
-but you'd better go, boy!
-I can't do that!
You can't even touch me,
let alone fight!
Smart move! Don't let go!
He can't get away now.
Surrender?
Wait, you're not...
Got it, huh?
It's not that I'm fast.
I just become
an electric current
and travel instantly
through space.
In water, I am invincible!
Impressive ice powers.
Ease up.
If you push too hard,
you're gonna collapse.
Ice won't conduct.
Let's see what else you've got.
Hmph!
Lakes and seas, clouds and sky,
by this talisman in my hand.
Rain shall cover all the land!
Dad!
Oh, no. A rain spell.
End it now!
Too late!
Now you're doomed!
We're coming, master!
Master, are you okay?
Why would you
sacrifice your arm?
I wasn't gonna take your life.
Disciples, hear me.
Prep these demons for transport.
Stop, stop! Your arms!
All of you, drop them!
Might I ask you,
-are you from the Chan sect?
-That's right.
Ah...
These are immortals
from Yu Xu Palace.
You mustn't be disrespectful.
Entering Yu Xu Palace
and learning
the teachings within
might not be a bad thing.
All of you,
you must lay down your weapons.
-Dad!
-Xiaobao, why have you returned?
Xiaobao! You must stand down!
Xiaobao!
Demon, time to put you down.
Stop! No!
Dad!
Nezha, freeze the river now!
You can't escape!
-Dad!
-Go! Son, go!
Now run!
Dad!
There's no escape.
-Move!
-He was defending his father.
Why take it so far?
Panax notojinseng,
cattail pollen,
munjeet, borneol...
-Loong's blood, safflower...
-Give me one more!
...angelica,
pseudo-ginseng powder,
sappanwood, poison nut.
My lord, now we have
everything on the list,
along with a hundred bushels
of sea bounty.
Our food stores
have been running low.
Master Shen, a moment.
We've had a meal prepared.
Would you honor us
with your presence?
You.
Oh, thanks
to Lord Li's kindness,
I've been taken in as a servant.
Though a demon,
he has a good heart.
As long as he behaves,
then he deserves a future too.
How do you like the food,
Master Shen?
It's not bad.
Then have some more, please.
Try some of the wine as well.
I don't drink. Immortals
must suppress our urges.
It is said
desire clouds the spirit.
It's also said
that with kindness comes virtue.
Talking won't work.
There's no way o-out for me.
Try and run,
but you can't hide forever.
The truth will find you
eventually.
If this path you walk
hurts more people,
you can fool the world,
but you will be the only fool.
And with your ascension,
where will you stand
when an immortal's duty
is to others in need?
Enough! What utter nonsense!
That's my duty?
You know nothing!
Sir! Someone's here
for Master Shen!
Brother...
Who did this to you?
Taoist priests.
They attacked Dad and I.
Dad had one of his arms...
cut off.
Who did it?
His... His name is...
Nezha.
Congratulations.
You passed again.
Uh, could you tell
Brother Wuliang?
Master is still in seclusion.
Refining pills.
Before the third trial,
why don't you rest
for a few days first?
We only got two days, kiddo.
Nah, I'm totally fine.
Let's do it.
Well, all right.
For your final trial,
Skull Mountain's Queen, Shi Ji.
Two urgent visitors
for Master Taiyi.
-Huh?
-Someone, help!
-Chentang Pass!
-It was our fault!
Dad?
Mom?
Dad!
Mom!
Hey, Nezha, don't panic!
Let's keep looking,
we'll find them!
I learned the news
as soon as I emerged.
Who could have committed
such a horrendous atrocity?
Greetings, master.
According to the Shieldos,
they were both struck
by a tremendous force
and lost consciousness.
When they came to, they found
Chentang Pass like this.
We haven't gotten
the elixir yet.
Why would they jump the gun
like that?
-Brother. You have an idea?
-Huh?
Um, no idea.
I was just thinking, uh,
where did all this lava
come from?
You're right. There's no
volcano near this place.
This is truly bizarre.
Oh, I found something.
From a demon?
This is a Loong print.
Impossible.
The Loongs are beneath
the Eastern Sea,
guarding the Suppression Seal.
None of them
could have gotten out.
Master, if I remember right,
the Loong Queen of Western Sea,
Ao Run,
she has a unique skill,
the sky-splitting...
Yes, her claw.
So she used
her Sky-Splitting Claw
to cross into Chentang Pass?
That would explain all the lava.
It must have been teleported
straight from
their fiery prison.
But the Loong King
keeps strict watch over her.
She couldn't have gotten out.
That leaves
only one possibility.
The thing that I feared the most
has just come to pass.
The Loong King betrayed us.
A grave accusation.
Could it be that
we've made a mistake?
It's no mistake.
They killed them!
What are you doing?
Wait a minute! Hey, hey, hey!
Are you heading to Loong Palace?
That's the way
to Skull Mountain.
What?
The Loongs
slaughtered innocents.
This is an unforgivable
atrocity.
Another summit
will take too long.
We'll strike first
and explain later.
Crana, go back to the palace.
Summon every Demon Hunter
in the Sect.
-Sir!
-Brother,
Nezha's parents
were slaughtered by demons.
We cannot let anything bad
happen to that boy.
You and Deero must make sure
he stays safe.
Of course.
I know you're heartbroken,
but can you please
just calm down?
First, can you take me home?
I'll go and confront my father,
make him explain!
And how will that
bring my parents back?!
Mirror, mirror on the wall,
who's the fairest one
within ten miles or more?
It's you, my lady.
And who's the fairest one
within a hundred miles?
It's you, my lady.
-What about a thousand?
-It's you.
-Ten thousand?
-You still.
-The entire world?
-You again.
You think I'm dumb?
Lie better at least!
No, no, I didn't want
to upset you.
I can take it!
Now tell me the truth
and I won't get mad.
Seriously? You mean that?
Although I have the beauty
of a goddess,
I know there's always someone
out there who's prettier!
-All right, ask away.
-Am I the fairest of them all?
-No.
-Oh, now, is that so hard?
Then tell me, am I the fairest
one within 10,000 miles?
-No.
-Okay, a thousand?
-You're not.
-A hundred?
-Ten miles?
-Should I lie?
Are you saying I'm not the
fairest one on this mountain?
-I'm sorry.
-Wait, what gives?!
There's not even another female
on this mountain!
But I'm a female.
You said that
you wouldn't get mad.
You prettier than me?
Come out, demon!
Hey, who are you calling demon?
It's Lady Shi Ji!
Little brat! Have we even met?
You should buy a girl
dinner first!
You'll be exposed!
Let me take over!
Stay out of this!
Do you honestly think you have
a chance at defeating me?
Every stone in this mountain
makes up my body.
Let's see you destroy me now!
Huh?
Use more force
and your body will collapse!
I said,
stay out of it!
- It's already started.
- Oh, boy. Not good, not good.
Everything hurts.
Good, there's a few pebbles!
I live on to fight another day!
Little brat!
You're gonna pay for this!
Nine-Loong Fire Trap!
You can't run. Ha!
Oh, kid,
why do you gotta be so rash?
Your body's almost had it.
Are you trying to die?
What was all that fire earlier?
Isn't Nezha an ice wielder?
Who told you that, huh? Frost,
flame, I taught him everything.
He's got combo powers.
Is that possible?
Come on, he's the Spirit Pearl.
Rules don't apply.
Hey, who taught him?
Me or you? You want my job, huh?
Forgive me, but I did sense
the strong presence of demonic
energy during the fight.
About that, uh, obviously
that's coming from her.
What did you say, fatty?!
I did not--
Was it you? Was it you?
Was it you? Just say it!
Yes, it was me! Stop shaking me!
I'm gonna hurl!
See? Told ya.
Nezha, you've passed
all the tests.
Today, I'll induct you through
a sacred rite: Ascension.
I remember when I first
became an immortal.
I was sweating through my shirt.
The Ascension Spell's longer
than I remember.
From now on, you're an immortal
of the Chan Sect.
This is
the Yu Xu Treasure Vault.
It houses all sorts
of rare magic items.
The Elixir Reparo.
You only get one.
Don't you need more time
to think?
The Elixir Reparo!
Yu Xu
has sent forth messengers
to inform the Twelve
about the Loong's crimes.
But they're leagues away,
and it'll take too long
for them to get here.
This time, I myself will lead
the hunt on Loongkind!
Nezha, will you and your spear
fight by my side?
I'm going back to Chentang Pass.
Then we'll take revenge
on the Loong King.
All right.
With your immense strength,
you can help tear down
Loong Palace.
After this, we're even.
Wait, don't leave!
When the ritual's done,
I'll go with you
to Loong Palace.
You know what I'm gonna do!
You being there
will only make it harder.
Next time we meet...
we'll be enemies.
Karma it is. Yeesh.
No, wait, you can't leave!
Your soul will scatter
if you go any further! Wait!
Nine-Loong Fire Trap!
Please calm down, will ya?
Going after him
won't change anything!
Leave me alone! Free me now!
No! I promised Nezha,
I've got to save you, kid!
Finally, air!
Who dares approach?
My name is Immortal Wuliang.
Ao Guang, admit your crime!
So... you found out?
Is Ao Bing still alive?
I'll accept your punishment,
but please spare my son,
-I beg you!
-Save your breath!
Heaven's Court ordered you
to guard the Abyss monsters.
Instead, you joined with them
to butcher Chentang Pass.
We did what?
Your clan's crimes
go beyond the pale.
Today, heaven's justice
shall be done!
By earth and sky,
with boundless might,
oh, great Tianyuan,
cleanse them with light!
Open!
Show yourselves!
What have you fools done
to Chentang Pass?
Only what you asked us to.
Follow Master Shen's orders.
Shen Gongbao?
Time's running out.
Better to focus on the present.
My lord,
we cannot just sit here!
I cannot leave him!
-The Suppression Seal!
-Leave the seal to us, my king.
Working together, we can
give you the time you require.
Fine.
I've had enough!
Wretched demon!
A chance like this
comes only once a millennium!
Break through the seal!
Raze their palace!
Soul-Shattering Blade!
Old fool! Now die!
All this demon energy,
aren't you afraid
that you'll be exposed?
I told you, if you dared
to hurt Chentang Pass,
I'd smash your palace
into pieces!
Tell me, does Ao Bing
still live?
Move it! Out of my way!
Ow!
Rise!
Do you have a death wish?
It won't be long
before you fade to dust!
I don't care if I live or die,
as long as you're dead!
Now to seal!
Look at what you've done!
Is the destruction of our kind
really what you fools want?
The chains...
Even the Loong King himself
can't match your power.
It seems that I was right
after all.
You're exactly what our order
needs right now.
Your parents spent their lives
fighting evil,
and now you must carry on
their legacy
and wipe out demonkind.
Let me rain down vengeance
on your behalf
and turn these beasts to pills.
- Now to my side!
- Master!
Nezha.
-Nezha.
- Dad?
- Nezha!
- Mom?
Nezha!
My boy, are you all right?
Your body...
I...
They already know about
who you and Ao Bing really are.
I... I thought...
I'd never see you again.
The spell's not finished yet.
Master still needs more time.
Nezha! My father
didn't destroy Chentang Pass!
All along,
the culprit was Wuliang!
Shieldos!
Loongs!
Brother! It's been forever!
What are you doing here?
Shen Gongbao,
you scheme with Loongs.
What are you planning?
I could ask the--
The same thing!
You took my father!
What are you planning?
Who said I took your father?
Only you knew
where my village was.
Without your order,
Nezha and your lackeys
wouldn't have captured him!
And my brother's arrow wound!
One look tells me, Deero,
your disciple, shot him!
Now there's the special talent
that I recruited.
Nothing ever slips past you,
now does it?
After all, I've done
your dirty work for centuries.
I also can guess why you've come
to put on this show
in Chentang Pass.
You're here to--
To frame the Loongs!
Repaying your mentor
with baseless accusations?
You've always u-used me
as a tool.
So between us,
there's only hate!
May I interest you in a deal,
master?
As steward of Yu Xu Palace,
you must know how to unhinge
the Sea-Stabilizing Chains.
I do.
What of it?
You--? You are going to rebel?
Ages ago, we four
fought the celestial realm.
Who first betrayed us
to the prison of our purgatory?
Now that Wuliang targets
Ao Guang,
we can take our revenge!
They say Chan Sect's leader
recruits without bias.
Our many abilities,
I trust you're aware of them?
If you unbind our chains
and help us gain immortality,
our humble service
will be yours.
Along with the Spirit Pearl
and Demon Orb's secret.
-They have a secret?
-Pathetic!
Where's your p-pride
and your sense of resistance?
We were young and foolish!
A thousand years in chains,
it has taught us well
about the rules.
And the rulers.
Smart choice.
But you're far too unruly.
How can I trust you?
Unless you let me place
upon you all--
We are willing.
The three Loongs
willingly allowed
Wuliang to put a curse on them.
If they dare disobey,
Wuliang can take their lives
at any moment.
Wuliang then fulfilled
his promise,
freeing them all from
the Sea-Stabilizing Chains.
When someone might rise
to challenge him,
he stages massacres,
frames others,
and sends troops
to capture them.
According to Shen Gongbao,
he himself had carried out
many such schemes for Wuliang
in exchange for a chance
to join the Chan Sect.
This time, Wuliang came
to destroy Chentang Pass
and frame the Loongs
of Eastern Sea.
But the unexpected happened
and he recruited
the Loong lords.
Then, from his new servants,
he learned the Demon Orb
and Spirit Pearl's secret.
After,
they deliberately left behind
a pair of clueless survivors
who'd seek out the Sect
and tell their story.
Seeing no hope of escape,
Shen Gongbao devised a plan.
The Yaksha,
he'd petrify us both,
then go into hiding
in the city sewers.
He'd wait until it was safe,
then come revive us.
And yourself?
My family's gone.
I have nothing left to live for.
Over there!
After him!
When a sect captures demons,
the story we're told are lies.
They are not being reformed
in Yu Xu Palace.
Instead, they're cast down
in the Tianyuan Cauldron
by Wuliang,
refined into pills,
used for Chan dominance!
Brother, how could you commit
such atrocities?
What--?
What will you say to our master
after everything he's taught us?
Now you know the truth about
the crimes Wuliang's committed.
Stop this before it's too late.
Take him back to Yu Xu,
so he may face justice!
The Demon Hunters
were trained by Master Wuliang.
You think a few cheap words
would turn us against him?
So I was wrong about the Loongs.
Let them all go!
I got your back!
You've betrayed us!
Just like you did, brother.
That was only to protect
our future.
I had no choice!
Well, now, to protect my future,
neither do I.
My queen, wait for us, please!
Don't leave us behind!
My king, take us with you!
My queen! My king!
You have all been sold out!
The Southern King.
The Northern King.
The Western Queen.
Nephew, come play a game
with your uncle.
Eat this!
Ax of Hellfire!
Flaming Ember Wheels!
Goes around and around
and around!
Want some more?
Little punk! You call that heat?
Your body's had it.
Don't push too hard.
For what I've done,
I'd give everything
to make sure
that the Loongs are free.
These kids can fight, huh?
Come dance with Auntie,
little one.
Huh?
- Bullying a child.
- Shame on you!
Hey! I'm your master's brother!
Elder abuse! How dare you!
It's no good. They're too fast.
Then let's change it up.
How about some mist?
Yeah.
Kill them.
Watch your backs in the mist.
Huh?
I have you now.
Watch where
you're swinging that!
Brother?
Uh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Nezha!
Surprise!
Disguise spell.
-Are you nuts?
-You can't fool me!
-Huh?
-Huh? Which one's fake?
Password.
She sells seashells by the...?
-What?
-He doesn't know it. It's him!
You really are the fake!
What is happening?
That's right! Huh?!
-Password.
-Uh, he sells--
He sells bells in the big well
by the lake?
Wrong!
It goes like this:
She sells seashells
by the seashore.
But I'm the real one!
How come I can't remember
the password?
'Cause we just made it up.
Can you make it easier?
It's too hard!
You idiot!
Stay away, you faker!
I'm the real Ao Shun.
That's crap.
You don't know the code.
Yeah, you don't either.
True. Does that mean I'm a fake?
Oh, brother.
Tai Chi align
with nature's flow.
Samadhi's fire,
cook pills below.
What are you scared of?
We used to bathe in lava
like it's nothing!
Ow! Ow! Hot! Hot! Hot!
Oh, no. It's Samadhi's Fire!
Stop your staring.
If anyone should eat me,
it's gonna be me.
Yummy.
Let my father go!
Freeze.
The Spirit Pearl.
What a perfect match
for our Demon Orb.
Ao Bing!
Freeze.
Huh?! The Heart-Piercing Curse?
Since I already knew
your true identities,
how could I not have
a backup plan?
Impossible.
That curse is complicated.
When did you cast it?
Oh! That's why your ascension
spell took forever.
You slipped the curse in.
Your dark powers,
even they won't break my
Heart-Piercing Curse so quickly.
A thousand spikes have pierced
through your nerves and veins.
So trying to move
will just tear you apart
from the inside.
No wonder I couldn't sense
anyone living in the city.
You were petrified.
But by staying alive,
you've only doomed Nezha.
Spirit Pearl.
Demon Orb.
You're both treasures.
We might have achieved
great things together.
But now all you'll become
are pills.
-Ao Bing!
-Father.
You... You're still alive!
It's a curse
from Master Wuliang.
He also framed the Loongs
for Chentang Pass.
Father, Nezha was deceived.
Don't blame him!
This is between you and me.
Leave my parents out of it!
Killing you now
will change nothing.
All of us are doomed
to die here.
If any one of you
still holds a grudge,
step forth, then.
Brother, how could you?
The Chan Sect
stands for what's right!
How could you go
and do something so horrible?
You must stop now.
Why not confess to master, huh?
I'll even vouch for you. Just--
You naive simpleton.
If our dominance
was truly secure,
or if you pampered children
took things seriously,
since all demons clearly do,
I'd never have gone
to such lengths.
Even if it means I'm damned,
that I'm hated,
it was a fair price for
the Chan Sect to reign supreme.
My conscience...
Conscience.
My conscience is clear.
Another one's done!
I'm beyond stuffed.
-You should try me.
-Thanks, pal.
When one of my fins are done,
you should try me too.
Uh, crab claws, anyone?
Plenty to go around. Huh?
What's going on? I...
My body, I can't feel my...
He's a pill now!
But I'm so young.
I don't wanna die!
No, please! Let me out!
Somebody help us!
Stay calm.
Focus all of your energy.
Each second counts.
Just hold on!
Son, you're stronger than I am.
You can still get through.
If you hold out
until the curse fades,
you'll have a chance to escape.
The Heart-Piercing Curse takes
at least six hours to wear off.
I'm afraid
I won't last that long.
-My love!
-Mom!
-Wake up, Mom.
-Nezha.
Nezha?
-Nezha!
-Mom, I'm right here!
You guys have to stay strong.
Don't mind me.
Try and just stay focused.
I'm fine though. Mom,
I don't feel the flames at all.
Nothing can kill you, boy.
If I remember correctly,
Demon Orb's flames and Samadhi's
Fire are from the same source.
Then the Tianyuan Cauldron
can't harm you.
That's right.
I must have forgotten.
Useless.
This is only my avatar.
Just as I thought,
you're indestructible.
That explains
the Supreme Lord's judgment.
Destroy you
with the Wrath of Heaven.
Well, Nezha, I can see
that you're a good son.
Why don't I give you a chance
to prove that?
The Oblivion Pill.
If you swallow this pill,
I shall spare
both your parents' lives.
Come, now.
My ways may seem cruel at first,
but I always keep my word.
If not, why would all those
demon elites I recruited
choose to serve?
You just have to swallow,
and I will swear to heaven,
I'll let your parents go free.
- Hmm?
- What are you doing?
Threatening a child
with the lives of his parents?
You think you're a god?
You're worse than any demon!
Nezha! Please, just leave us be.
You have to survive this, son.
Hold on until the curse breaks,
or your two brothers
can come find you.
You think that I can't destroy
the Demon Orb?
It's only just a matter of time.
Once you both are dead,
I have a hundred ways
I can kill him.
I just don't want
to die for nothing.
Why won't you let me
sacrifice myself?
Why won't you let me do it?
If your traded your life
for your mother and me,
do you think either of us could
ever find peace in this life?
Nezha.
No, Mom! Stop, please.
-It'll hurt you.
-It's okay.
This is it.
Mommy just wants one last hug.
Mom!
Guess I won't be seeing you
grow up.
You must be brave...
and walk your own path.
I... I'm no good.
I'm just useless.
You gave birth to a demon.
And I've only hurt you
this whole time.
All I wanted
was to make you proud.
It's all my fault!
I'm sorry.
Mom.
I'm sorry!
Every moment I spent with you,
I was so happy.
None of it mattered.
Immortal or demon.
All I know is...
that you are my son.
Mommy will always...
- Nezha, you must stay calm.
- Stop!
Your body will be ripped
to shreds!
Samadhi's Fire compensated
for the fire needed
to rebuild his body.
His physical form...
is complete!
Dad.
Take care of Mom.
We're breaking out.
Oh, no. They're absorbing
the cauldron's energy.
Roots of Power!
Now, Hunters,
by my command, march!
Father, you must save
your energy for the flames.
We have been backing down
for too long.
We thought if we gave him
everything,
then Wuliang would let us live.
But in the end, they still want
to see us dead.
Well, if that's
what they want, argh,
then I guess we'll just have
to fight them to the death!
Yeah! To the death!
We mustn't let any escape.
Do not give up!
Keep pushing!
Make it break!
No, my cauldron.
The Chan Sect's foundation. No.
Kill every last one
of these beasts!
Fight!
You traitors are still siding
with the bad guys?
Heard of morals?
Roaring Loong Waves!
So those two minions of his
are both monsters too.
Demons, Immortals.
All of it's a part
of your trickery!
King of the vermin,
how dare you stand against me!
Now you'll witness
my true power.
I value talent,
so I will give you both
one last chance.
Surrender now
and I'll make you immortal.
To hell with you immortals!
I'm all demon.
So what?!
You claim to serve the light,
but all you do
is prey upon the weak
and bring chaos to the world.
You're the one who's truly evil!
Ignorant fools.
Immortals rule this world.
Only those who side
with the strong survive.
Either accept that fact
or there'll be
nowhere safe to run.
If there's no place that's safe,
I'll just have to make one
myself!
And if I can't be who I am,
I'll just have to change
the world!
Master!
Not my face.
Not my face!
You... You fools broke the seal
on my Ageless Spell.
You old fart!
Back to Yu Xu.
Wait for me!
My father
will lead our clan away,
deep into the ocean to hide.
Now that they know your secret,
why don't you come with us?
No.
I've been hiding all my life,
running from what I really am.
Now I finally know
how I have to face the world.
Wuliang's
one of the Supreme Lord's
most powerful lieutenants.
He won't fall easily.
Plus, the Immortals' world
spurns demonkind.
Immortals and demons?
Those are just made-up names
for those in charge to control.
So they might be.
You think anything you do
will change that?
Just watch me.
Fighting against the world...
Perhaps I'm just too old
for that kind of battle.
Ao Bing.
I know by now
that once you've decided,
you'll see it to the end.
My son, in the past,
I put too much
of a burden on you.
I never cared to ask
what you think.
For that, I am sorry.
I only wished to use
what I'd gone through
to give you a better life.
But now I realize,
a parent's journey, it lives
in the past, but you do not.
And your path
should be yours alone.
So now... follow your heart,
wherever it takes you.
I knew that you'd come back.
Why's that?
'Cause we're both way too young.
Too young to fear.
Master, your face.
It's fine.
Crana already took care of it.
The cauldron's gone.
Now Chan Sect dominance
is at risk.
And we've committed
an unforgivable crime.
We must act now
before our master emerges again.
Come, time for a visit.
Is his holding cell
hidden enough?
No one else will come here.
The cell's also shielded
from magic,
and only you and the one guard
we posted can open the gate.
Hmm.
Slacking off?
Have nice dreams?
-What's going on?
-This gate scans your face.
Since your appearance
has changed,
you must re-register.
Fine, then.
Laughing at me, eh?
Have a ten-year nap.
You've suffered, brother.
You're the one who's suffered.
Tell me, who did this
to your face?
Do you know the real reason
I recruited you to the sect?
I found myself
in need of a demon.
The Great War is nigh.
When it arrives,
you will prove to be
quite useful.
Like hell!
Father! Father!
Don't worry.
He's still breathing.
If you allow me
place to a curse upon you,
he'll lead a comfortable life
at Yu Xu Palace.
Your two guests have arrived,
master.
I'll give you
some time to think.
Hmm?
The medicine seems to be
working.
Well, what now, then?
Who else can open it?
Ten years.
Of Wulong Cloud Cave, Jinzha.
Of Jiugong Crane Cave, Muzha.
Ready to serve.
Master, just bear with us.
I think that's enough.
It seems the left eye's
not swollen.
Get the right cheek too.
Hold it. Were you laughing at me
just now?
We wouldn't dare.
You're suffering.
It truly pains us
to see you this way.
-Really?
-Of course, master.
We swear to heaven.
All right, all right, all right!
I might have lost control.
-You what?
-Don't worry.
Put it on
and we'll start again.
Master,
you're meant for greatness.
This is all for
the Chan Sect's future.
Just a few more tries.
We'll get it right eventually.
Don't let him get away!
Take your hands off me!
Quick! I got him! Rub it on!
Let go of me!